

¡Hola! — Soy diseñador de producto con conocimientos de desarrollo front-end. Estoy particularmente interesado en la **experiencia del usuario, la usabilidad y la investigación**, así como sus aplicaciones para mejorar la vida de las personas. Mi lengua materna es el **español** y hablo **inglés** con fluidez.

Experiencia

Diseñador de producto — Emprendimiento

EventNest

Oct 2024 — Hoy

España — Remoto

I am working on the creation of a **marketplace** that helps event organizers and promoters find the services they need to develop their activities. The project is currently in its initial phase, where I am conducting the necessary research to define the **MVP** (Minimum Viable Product) to begin working on.

Diseñador de producto — Emprendimiento

Geomites

Mar 2023 — Hoy España — Remoto

I lead the UX and UI design of this project, where we are designing and developing a **mobile video**game for iOS and Android platforms in an agile environment.

Diseñador de producto — Freelance

Abr 2022 — Hoy

España — Remoto

I work as a product designer for different companies and sectors. My main freelance activities include designing and developing **company websites**, designing **corporate documents**, and participating in the **design process** of various products or services.

Responsable de marketing — Contratado

Promam

Jul 2017 — Sep 2021 España — In situ

I was responsible for marketing and design tasks, managing the design and development of the **company's website** and led **SEO** positioning campaigns. I spearheaded marketing campaigns on social media and organized and developed the design of various products necessary for the company's operations, including **catalogs, advertisements, and documents**. I also collaborated with stakeholders to organize the **marketing and sales strategy**.

Educación

Google & Coursera, Interaction Design Foundation

2021 - Present

Pensamiento de diseño: La guía definitiva, Experiencia del usuario: Guía para principiantes, Fundamentos de la experiencia de usuario, Investigación de usuarios, Psicología Gestalt, Interacción persona-ordenador, Diseño para el siglo XXI, Diseño emocional, Visualización de la información, Experiencia de usuario, Diseño visual, Patrones de diseño.

Universidad Rey Juan Carlos

Grado en Marketing

2011 - 2016

Habilidades

Investigación UX, Diseño UX, Diseño UI, Wireframing, Prototipado, Resolución de problemas, Comunicación, Sistemas de diseño, Usabilidad.

Herramientas

Sketch, Figma, Adobe Creative suite, Framer, Webflow, Wordpress, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Axure, Asana, Jira, ChatGPT, Midjourney, NotebookLM

Contacto

<u>alejandromorenomartin.com</u> +34 618110583 alejandromorenomartin1990@gmail.com